<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | The Yansong Social Neuroscience Lab</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alumni</title>
      <link>/author/alumni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/alumni/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Qianqian was a research assistant in the lab. She received her B.A. of Psychology from Rutgers University in New Jersey, United States. She is interested in emotion perception, impression formation and prejudice. She is a big cartoon lover and enjoys drawing during her spare time. She also has a great passion for food and her favorite food is hot pot.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alumni</title>
      <link>/author/alumni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/alumni/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shucheng was a master student in the lab. She received her B.A. in Economics from Shanghai Business School in Shanghai, China and has graduated in June 2019 from Nanjing University. Her project is on characterizing social support in intimate relationships. She has now joined Zhenai corporation as a research staff.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alumni</title>
      <link>/author/alumni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/alumni/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yuan was a master student in the lab. She received her B.A. in Management from Hubei University of Education in Wuhan, China. Her master project is related to how social rank influences decision making in material and moral dilemmas using behavioral measures and tDCS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alumni</title>
      <link>/author/alumni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/alumni/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yaxin was a master student in the lab. She received her B.A. in Psychology from Jilin University in Jilin,China. Her project is related to exploring how integration of rewarding cue information influences human executive functions using the combination of EEG and fMRI techniques.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alumni</title>
      <link>/author/alumni/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/alumni/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Zixiang used to a master student in my lab and has graduated in June 2019. He focused on a project on neural correlates of sexual dysfunctions in patients with premature ejaculation using the fMRI technique. He now works in Tengxun company.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD Student</title>
      <link>/author/phd-student/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/phd-student/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chengguo is the first-year PhD student in the lab. She received her M.A. ii Psychology from Suzhou University. Her project is related to the neurophysiological mechanisms underlying perceptions of social dominance and social dominance formation using electrophysiological methods (e.g., scalp EEG and iEEG)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD Student</title>
      <link>/author/phd-student/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/phd-student/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Quqian is the first-year PhD student in the lab.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD Student</title>
      <link>/author/phd-student/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/phd-student/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Xi is currently a second-year Ph.D  student in the lab. Before joining the lab, she used to be a research assistant at Beijing Normal University. She is interested in neuropsychological mechanisms underlying the role of social competition on false memory using behavioral measures and brain imaging methods.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PhD Student</title>
      <link>/author/phd-student/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/phd-student/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Zhenliang is currently a Ph.D student in my lab. He is interested in how competition and competitive outcomes modulates human social behavior (such as risk-taking, cooperation and executive function) using brain imaging methods (e.g., fNIRS and ERP ).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principal Investigator</title>
      <link>/author/principal-investigator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/principal-investigator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am a Principal Investigator in the Institute for Brain Sciences and at the Department of Psychology, Nanjing University, China. I received my master degree in Psychology in the State Key Lab of Cognitive Neuroscience and Learning, Beijing Normal University. Then I went to Cognitive Neurology Group at Max Planck Institute for Neurological Research as a guest internship and a Ph.D student.  I received my Ph.D. in Cognitive Neuroscience from CNRS and pursued my postdoc in the same lab in Lyon, France.&lt;br&gt;
I am interested in neuropsychological mechanisms underlying human social behaviors and how competition influences these processes.&lt;br&gt;
Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:yansongli@nju.edu.cn&#34;&gt;yansongli@nju.edu.cn&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:liyansongrenzs@gmail.com&#34;&gt;liyansongrenzs@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate Research Assistant</title>
      <link>/author/undergraduate-research-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/undergraduate-research-assistant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m Wu Hejia from Jilin province. I hope during my undergraduate period, I can lay a solid foundation for my future study and enrich my learning ability.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate Research Assistant</title>
      <link>/author/undergraduate-research-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/undergraduate-research-assistant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a junior student in Nanjing university. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in human social behaviors and how reward influences these processes.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Undergraduate Research Assistant</title>
      <link>/author/undergraduate-research-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/undergraduate-research-assistant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’m now a third-year undergraduate student in the Department of Applied Psychology, Nanjing University. I am interested in social competition and social cognition. I plan to explore the relationship between stigma and social competition. I have a wide range of hobbies, such as photography, traveling, dancing and playing badminton.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visiting Student</title>
      <link>/author/visiting-student/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/author/visiting-student/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tiantian is the third year Ph.D. student at Shanghai Normal University. She is currently a visiting researcher in the lab. She received her M.D. in Psychology from Minnan Normal University in Zhangzhou, China. She is now work on a project about how social rank influences individuals&amp;rsquo; risky decision making.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
